[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest living terrestrial organism on the planet?", "correct_answer": "African Bush Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["African Forest Elephant", "Asian Elephant", "Indian Elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest mall in the USA.", "correct_answer": "The King of Prussia Mall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center", "The Bergen Mall", "The Mall at 4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word abacus derives from a Hebrew word, meaning this.", "correct_answer": "Dust", "incorrect_answers": ["Movement", "Sky", "Wood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these is NOT a type of wombat?", "correct_answer": "Arid Central", "incorrect_answers": ["Common", "Southern Hairy Nosed", "Northern Hairy Nosed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The epicardium is also known as the visceral pericardium.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who played the brother, Dwayne, in Little Miss Sunshine, won rave reviews for his  role in L.I.E.", "correct_answer": "Paul Dano", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Danes", "Don Newcombe", "Robert Newsome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a major difference between New World monkeys (Platyrrhines) and Old World Monkeys (Cercopithecidae)?", "correct_answer": "New World Monkeys can hang by their tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Old world monkeys lack sitting pads.", "Old World Monkeys have canines that can chew meat", "New World monkeys can not walk on two legs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Nicholas Cage, who plays the role of Ghost Rider in the 2007 movie of the same name, has a Ghost Rider tattoo in real life.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1960, a  #1 hit on the pop charts was the comedy song Please Mr. Custer, I Dont Wanna Go!. Whose song was it?", "correct_answer": "Larry Vernes", "incorrect_answers": ["Bill Hayes", "Tommy Hartigans", "B.B. Thompsons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who kills Vito Corleone?", "correct_answer": "No one, he just dies", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Corleone", "Don Emilio Barzini", "Kay Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first non-Muslim to make the journey from mecca to Medina?", "correct_answer": "Richard Burton", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Stanley", "Ronald Kateman", "Richard the Lion Hearted"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1996 movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 69th Academy Awards in 1997?", "correct_answer": "The English Patient", "incorrect_answers": ["Shine", "Secrets  Lies", "Jerry Maguire"]}]